Finding Aid for Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated
Clarke Historical Library
- Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated.
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Zawacki, Alexander J., Art,undated (Box 65, Folder 129)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Zorn, George A.,undated (Box 65, Folder 130)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Zeoli, Harold W., Math,undated (Box 65, Folder 131)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Zorn, Marilyn,undated (Box 65, Folder 132)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Adams, Karen,undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Wheeler, Elizabeth L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Arnett, Carroll,undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Bailey, James H.,undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Barnard, Anna M.,undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Barnard, Edith,undated (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Barnes, Charles C.,undated (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Beck, E. C.,undated (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Beddow, Ira A.,undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Bedo, Andrew, M.D.,undated (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Bellows, Charles,undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Bennett, Lyle,undated (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Blankenship, Jan,undated (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Bomzer, Herbert,undated (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Bovee, Norvall C.,undated (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Bowen, Elbert R.,undated (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Bowman, James E.,undated (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Bradshaw, James S.,undated (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Briggs, Edgar V.,undated (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Brown, Edward,undated (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Browne, William P.,undated (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Brooks, Kendall,undated (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Bulger, Margery,undated (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Burns, Oran F.,undated (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Bush, Fred R.,undated (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Calkins, R.D.,undated (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Carey, Joseph P.,undated (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Carlin, Leslie,undated (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Carlson, A. A.,undated (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Carr, Lucile,undated (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Carson, John F.,undated (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Chambers, Ima M.,undated (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Chien, Gabriel,undated (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Cobb, Bertha M. Ronan,undated (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Cofer, Lloyd M.,undated (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Comer, Ralph L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 36)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Colness R. Cedric,undated (Box 66, Folder 37)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Cook, Theodore,undated (Box 66, Folder 38)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Cratin, Paul D.,undated (Box 66, Folder 39)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Csendes, Joseph F.,undated (Box 66, Folder 40)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Cuff, Roger P.,undated (Box 66, Folder 41)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Curry, Herbert L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 42)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Curry, Laverne L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 43)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Cuthbert, N. L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 44)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Dain, Floyd R.,undated (Box 66, Folder 45)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Decker, Keith M.,undated (Box 66, Folder 46)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Dees, Levi O.,undated (Box 66, Folder 47)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Doby, Harry R.,undated (Box 66, Folder 48)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Donald, Ernest Paul,undated (Box 66, Folder 49)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: DePuy, George Fred,undated (Box 66, Folder 50)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Dunbar, Winsor S.,undated (Box 66, Folder 51)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Dunsdon, Rollin O.,undated (Box 66, Folder 52)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Ellis, Art,undated (Box 66, Folder 53)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Emry, Hazel T.,undated (Box 66, Folder 54)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Eaton, Orville,undated (Box 66, Folder 55)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Ellsberg, Alan W.,undated (Box 66, Folder 56)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Enders, Calvin W.,undated (Box 66, Folder 57)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Erikson, Leo,undated (Box 66, Folder 58)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Evett, Paul L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 59)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Fagerstrom, Dalphy I.,undated (Box 66, Folder 60)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Farhat, Leo A.,undated (Box 66, Folder 61)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Fell, Robert G.,undated (Box 66, Folder 62)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Filson, Malcolm H.,undated (Box 66, Folder 63)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Firestone, Bernard J.,undated (Box 66, Folder 64)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Foley, Margaret A.,undated (Box 66, Folder 65)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Folkert, Kendall W.,undated (Box 66, Folder 66)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Form, Arnold L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 67)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Frear, Scott E.,undated (Box 66, Folder 68)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Gill, John G.,undated (Box 66, Folder 69)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Grawn, Charles T.,undated (Box 66, Folder 70)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Devens, Carol,undated (Box 66, Folder 71)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Barbara P. Greene,undated (Box 66, Folder 72)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Grove, Eugene F.,undated (Box 66, Folder 73)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Gruber, Leslie,undated (Box 66, Folder 74)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Hammack, J. Alan,undated (Box 66, Folder 75)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Hampton, Raymond E.,undated (Box 66, Folder 76)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Hansen, Lorentz,undated (Box 66, Folder 77)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Hanson, Robert D.,undated (Box 66, Folder 78)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Hays, Robert D.,undated (Box 66, Folder 79)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Hepler, John C.,undated (Box 66, Folder 80)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Herron, Russell L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 81)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Hinshaw, Dean O.,undated (Box 66, Folder 82)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Hobson, Stephen G.,undated (Box 66, Folder 83)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Hodgins, James,undated (Box 66, Folder 84)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Howe, Karl F.,undated (Box 66, Folder 85)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Irwin, John,undated (Box 66, Folder 86)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Johnson, Helen L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 87)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Johnson, Neal Leroy,undated (Box 66, Folder 88)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: O’Connell, Catherine,undated (Box 66, Folder 89)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Oppenheimer, O.,undated (Box 66, Folder 90)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Osborn, John K.,undated (Box 66, Folder 91)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Park, Charles B.,undated (Box 66, Folder 92)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Park, Charles V.,undated (Box 66, Folder 93)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Owen, James,undated (Box 66, Folder 94)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Pearce, Webster,undated (Box 66, Folder 95)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Pfeiffer, Charles F.,undated (Box 66, Folder 96)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Pfister, Emil R.,undated (Box 66, Folder 97)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Pike, C. Milton, Jr.,undated (Box 66, Folder 98)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Poole, Charles P.,undated (Box 66, Folder 99)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Potter, Mary K.,undated (Box 66, Folder 100)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Powell, Richard L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 101)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Powers, J. Harold,undated (Box 66, Folder 102)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Praeger, Ethel May,undated (Box 66, Folder 103)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Jorae, Irene L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 104)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Kelly, Kenneth (Bill),undated (Box 66, Folder 105)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Khoury, Sari,undated (Box 66, Folder 106)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Knapp, Thomas S.,undated (Box 66, Folder 107)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Koeninger, Rupert C.,undated (Box 66, Folder 108)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: LaLonde, John G.,undated (Box 66, Folder 109)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Lamont, John D.,undated (Box 66, Folder 110)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Lantz, P. F.,undated (Box 66, Folder 111)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Larzelere, Claude S.,undated (Box 66, Folder 112)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Lawton, David L.,undated (Box 66, Folder 113)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Lichtenfelt, Richard J.,undated (Box 66, Folder 114)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Lieberman, Leonard,undated (Box 66, Folder 115)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Lieberman, Leslie,undated (Box 66, Folder 116)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Loughridge, Rachel,undated (Box 66, Folder 117)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Love, Claude D.,undated (Box 66, Folder 118)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Lutz, Donald,undated (Box 66, Folder 119)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Maldonado, Luis,undated (Box 66, Folder 120)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Marcus, J. D.,undated (Box 66, Folder 121)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Maple, Robert P.,undated (Box 66, Folder 122)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Marshall, Herbert E.,undated (Box 66, Folder 123)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Martin, Francis,undated (Box 66, Folder 124)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Mathis, Paul Carl, II,undated (Box 66, Folder 125)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Maybee, Harper C.,undated (Box 66, Folder 126)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Maybee, Rolland,undated (Box 66, Folder 127)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: McCarley, Walter W.,undated (Box 66, Folder 128)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: McKenna, Edward E.,undated (Box 66, Folder 129)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: McKenny, Charles,undated (Box 66, Folder 130)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: McManamon, James E.,undated (Box 66, Folder 131)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: McNamara, Jane,undated (Box 66, Folder 132)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: McNeel, Wakelin, Jr.,undated (Box 66, Folder 133)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Mefort, C. J.,undated (Box 66, Folder 134)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Merrill, Ernest J.,undated (Box 66, Folder 135)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Millar, Margaret S.,undated (Box 66, Folder 136)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Mitchell, Henry,undated (Box 66, Folder 137)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Moore, Wilbur E.,undated (Box 66, Folder 138)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Nelson, George H.,undated (Box 66, Folder 139)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Nixon, Patricia Ann,undated (Box 66, Folder 140)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Noble, Hanson,undated (Box 66, Folder 141)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Lt. Col. William Nolde,undated (Box 66, Folder 142)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Belck, Nancy,undated (Box 66, Folder 143)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Robert Braunlich,undated (Box 66, Folder 144)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Carson, L. Michael,undated (Box 66, Folder 145)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Doyle, C. Patrick,undated (Box 66, Folder 146)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Foster, Dina,undated (Box 66, Folder 147)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: John, Gay,undated (Box 66, Folder 148)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Ghanem, Salma I.,undated (Box 66, Folder 149)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Grigaliunas, William J.,undated (Box 66, Folder 150)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Hill, James,undated (Box 66, Folder 151)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Kerr, J. David,undated (Box 66, Folder 152)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Kissen, Rita,undated (Box 66, Folder 153)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Rose Marshall,undated (Box 66, Folder 154)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: McLauchlin, Robert,undated (Box 66, Folder 155)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Michaud, Paul,undated (Box 66, Folder 156)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: News Central,undated (Box 66, Folder 157)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Peterson, William David,undated (Box 66, Folder 158)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Repp, Thomas J.,undated (Box 66, Folder 159)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Shelton, Maria M.,undated (Box 66, Folder 160)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Spivey, Sheryl,undated (Box 66, Folder 161)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Tchudi, Susan,undated (Box 66, Folder 162)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Trainor, Sheila,undated (Box 66, Folder 163)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Staff Meetings,undated (Box 66, Folder 164)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Wardrop, Mary,undated (Box 66, Folder 165)
  - News of Faculty R-Z: Ernest Yoder,undated (Box 66, Folder 166)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Roger Kessler [chair 1995, member 1995-2003],undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Kulhavi, John [1996-2001],undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Perry, Marnette [1999-2001],undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Rotter, Harriet B. [1993-2000],undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Smith, W. Sidney [chair 1994, 1991-2000],undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: CMU Information,undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Dambrot, Keith [men’s basketball coach, incident, 1991-1999],undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Davenport, Donita [women’s winning basketball coach, 1984-1996],undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Campbell, Jerry D. [chair 2000, 1995-2000],undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Caponigro, Jeffrey [chair 2008, 2002-2008],undated (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Comai, Stephanie [chair 2010, 2003-2010],undated (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Fabiano, James Sr. [chair 2004, 1970-1971, 2000-2005],undated (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Foster, Melanie Reinhold [chair 2003, 1998-2008],undated (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Kevin F. Kelly, undated,undated (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Dr. Sam Kottamasu [chair 2012, 2005-2012],undated (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Maryland, Patricia, Dr. [2011-2013],undated (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Torreano, Gail [chair 2009, 2003-2010],undated (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Ronald C. Edmonds [2018-],undated (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Fannon, Brian W. [chair 2013, 2007-2014],undated (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Garrett, Jacqueline [2007-2014],undated (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: Marilyn French Hubbard [2005-2012],undated (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - (.25 cu. ft. box): News of CMU. Bd of Trustees members: John D. Hurd [chair, 2013, 2009-2014],undated (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Colored Slides, As: Academic Assistance,undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Colored Slides, As: Academic Information,undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Colored Slides, As: Accounting Department,undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Colored Slides, As: Administration,undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Colored Slides, As: Administration 2,undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Colored Slides, As: Admission,undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Colored Slides, As: Aerials,undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Colored Slides, As: Alumni,undated (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Colored Slides, As: Alumni 2,undated (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Colored Slides, As: Art Department,undated (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Colored Slides, Bs: Baseball,undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Colored Slides, Bs: Baseball 2,undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Colored Slides, Bs: Baseball 3,undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Colored Slides, Bs: Basketball Men’s,undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Colored Slides, Bs: Basketball Men’s 2,undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Colored Slides, Bs: Women’s Basketball,undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Colored Slides, Bs: Women’s Basketball 2,undated (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Colored Slides, Bs: Between the ponds,undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Colored Slides, Bs: Beaver Island,undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Board of Trustees,undated (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Bohannon School,undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Broadcasting and Cinematic Arts,undated (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Business Administration,undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Business Services,undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: CMU Logo,undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Campus Scenics-Newer,undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Campus Scenics-Newest,undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Campus Scenics,undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Campus Scenics-Newer,undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Newest Campus Scenics,undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Campus Scenics [folder 1 of 2],undated (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Colored Slides, B-C: Campus Scenics [folder 2 of 2],undated (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Campus Scenics,undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Career Information Library,undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Career Services,undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Centralight,undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Chemistry Department,undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Cheerleaders,undated (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Chip Card,undated (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Chip Facilities,undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Clarke Historical Library,undated (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: College of Extended Learning,undated (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Commencement,undated (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Communication Disorders,undated (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Computer Science,undated (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Construction,undated (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Continuing Education,undated (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Counseling Center,undated (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Creative Arts Gallery,undated (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Cross Country,undated (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Dance,undated (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Development,undated (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Distance Learning,undated (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: English,undated (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Colored Slides, C-F: Field Hockey,undated (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Mixed Photographs, A-B, P: Alumni – Colored Photographs,undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Mixed Photographs, A-B, P: Art Department (photographs),undated (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Mixed Photographs, A-B, P: Athletics,undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Mixed Photographs, A-B, P: Athletic Training,undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Mixed Photographs, A-B, P: Banking,undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Mixed Photographs, A-B, P: Beaver Island,undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Mixed Photographs, A-B, P: Biology,undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Mixed Photographs, A-B, P: Board of Trustees,undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Mixed Photographs, A-B, P: Bookstore,undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Mixed Photographs, A-B, P: Physical Education,undated (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Mixed Photographs, A: Academic Assistance,undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Mixed Photographs, A: Activities,undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Mixed Photographs, A: Accounting Department,undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Mixed Photographs, A: Administration,undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Mixed Photographs, A: Admissions,undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Mixed Photographs, A: Advancement,undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Mixed Photographs, A: Advising,undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Mixed Photographs, A: Aerials Campus,undated (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Mixed Photographs, A: Affirmative Action,undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Mixed Photographs, A: Black and White Photographs Alumni,undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Mixed Photographs, A: Alumni colored Photographs,undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Broadcasting and Cinematics Arts,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Business,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Campus Scenic,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Campus Scenic, Group Photographs,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Career Services,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: CEEP Program,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Centralis Scholarship,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Centennial,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Center for Applied Research and Tech,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Charter School,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Chemistry,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Clarke Historical Library,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Classrooms,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: College of Extended Learning,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C: Commencement, Black and white,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Mostly Digital prints, B-C:Commencement, Color,2002-2008 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Centralight,undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Centralis,undated (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Century Club,undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Student Activities Concerts,undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Chemistry,undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Child Development Lab,undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Chippettes,undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Chip Center,undated (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Chippewa Club,undated (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Clarke Historical Library,undated (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: CMU And You Day,undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,December 1987 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: College of Extending Learning,undated (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Coaches with Family,undated (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,December 1980 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,May 1981 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,December 1981 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,May !982 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,December !982 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,May !983 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,December !983 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,1984 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,1985 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,1986 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Commencement,undated (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: CDO (Communication Disorders),undated (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Computer Science,undated (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Concerts,undated (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Continuing Education,undated (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Counseling Center,undated (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Copy Negatives,undated (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Crowds,undated (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Dance,undated (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Day Care Center,undated (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Counseling, Education Development,undated (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Mixed Files, C-E: Development Board,undated (Box 75, Folder 36)